

Mina AMROUCHE

Freelancer

Front-end developer

Contact details

mina.amrouche@iminait.com



+31 6 57 68 63 95



amrouche-a67b81115/





Technical skills





















Mysql (S) Php 🔑

Languages





Profile

5 years of web development taught me that coding is all about creating and constantly improving. The quality and the clarity of the code is crucial for sharing and maintaining it in the future, but it shouldn't be an obstacle when something needs to be done quickly.

Professional but easy-going, I'm not afraid to take initiative and work until a problem is solved within a team or independently. I always do my best to understand what's asked of me and give my advise when it can help.

Experience

Lead Front-end developer, UbiOps

Sep 2019 - June 2021

Built the front-end of UbiOps from scratch within 6 months on my own, then create a well-designed reliable REST API. I was in charge on the front-end releases and prioritizing tasks for internal improvements and requests from

Main technologies: ReactJS, Redux, MUI, Docker, Gitlab Cl, Kubernetes, Google Cloud.

Front-end developer, Saegus

Apr 2018 - May 2019

Fruitful collaboration with designers (UX, UI, graphic designers...) and data scientists. Development from scratch of several web applications for CAC40 companies: L'Oréal, Engie, Orange, TechnipFMC... Full project management including direct discussion with clients, costs estimation and development. Main technologies: ReactJS, Angular, NodeJS, Vue.

Fullstack web developer, Monsieur Biz

Sep 2016 - Mar 2018

agile methodology.

Education

Master in Computer Science, Epitech

Sep 2015 - Sep 2018

Paris, France

Mathematics / Computer science, Bachelor, 2nd

Sep 2014 - Sep 2015

vear

Faculté Saint-Charles, Marseille, France

Mathematics / Physics / Chemistry, Bachelor, 1st year

Sep 2013 - Sep 2014

Training & certification

Certification PSM I (Professional Scrum Master I)

Nov 2018

Score: 98.8% - Scrum.org

Symfony training

Sep 2016

Jolicode - Paris